Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel Legal Tow Nikle. The vehicle has met with an
accident, how to claim insurance.
This question comes to my mind
whenever any accident happens, it is our
vehicle's accident and
in this video of ours, we will try our best to answer all the
questions arising in your mind related to insurance plan.
Before starting the video, I
request all of you to subscribe to our channel
and press the bell icon button so that you will stay
updated with our next video.
Let us first know
what happens in insurance.
We are going to explain to you very simply about insurance claim.
Whenever we
buy a new vehicle or a second-hand vehicle, we get the
insurance of that vehicle done in our name.
While getting the insurance done, we pay the insurance
fee to the company from which we
get the insurance done.
After getting the insurance, we get interest on the insurance. The
date of getting the insurance done, the insurance number of your vehicle,
when is the insurance expiring and
other important facts are written on the insurance paper.
We get insurance done because if
any accident happens to any official, then the
damage caused in that accident is compensated by
your insurance.  We will present the questions that
come to people's minds regarding the plan
in the form of questions and answers here in our video.
Let's start with the
first question that
comes to our mind:
how to film a car accident? Whenever your car
collides with another car,
you should file a
First Information Report at the nearest police station from the accident spot. If
you are
not in a condition to go to the nearest police
station, then
inform the police about the accident by phone and
also call an ambulance for initial treatment.
Immediately after filing the First Information Report,
inform your insurance company and provide
complete details of the accident.
A server sent by the insurance company
creates an accident death report for the vehicle involved in the accident. This
accident death report goes to the insurance company
manager, who
passes the claim based on the terms and conditions of the insurance. It is
essential to be aware that whenever you have a car accident
and you want to click,
you should be insured
if your insurance has expired.
So you will not get the plane The
driver
must have a valid driving license
If the driver does not have a driving license,
you will not get interest The
driver's age should
not be less than 18 years under any circumstances
We tell you that if the driver is
less than 18 years of age, you will
not get insurance compensation The insurance plan will
reject your insurance and the
insurance policy cannot be reduced
Driving a vehicle without a valid driving license
You are working in London,
hence you will
not be able to make an insurance claim You do not have a driving license
and you were driving The
driver is
under 18 years of age The vehicle does not have registration, fitness
and permit The driver is drunk
Driving is a reaction and the driver
was drunk Accident claim will not be available
If the vehicle insurance policy has been violated then you
can claim Yes, you can get
a new duplicate insurance policy by paying a fee by giving a written notice to your insurance company after getting the vehicle insurance policy
Friends, stay
connected to our channel for such legal information
If you liked this video, then
subscribe to our channel
Now tell us your topic by commenting on Chronicle and
we will make the next video like this and bring it to
you.